Guide to the Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 3: Boxes 45-48
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 3: Boxes 45-48
- Box 46, Folder (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: American Telephone and Telegraph Company, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Out-of-Hour Activities, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Got a Heavy Date, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: A Thought for Tomorrow, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: You in a Business Career at Michigan Bell, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Careers for College Men, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Employees' Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Employees' Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Tone of Service, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Why Telephone Rates Went Up, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Health Information for Supervisory personnel, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Departmental Organization Charts, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: Departmental Organization Charts, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: Agreements Between Michigan Bell Telephone Company and Communications Workers of America, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: Memorandum of Agreement, Communications Workers of America and Michigan Bell Telephone Company and communications Workers of America, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: Memorandum of Agreement, Communications Workers of America and Michigan Bell Telephone Company and Communications Workers of America, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: Memorandum of Agreement, Communications Workers of America and Michigan Bell Telephone company an Communications Workers of America, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: Employees' Payroll Deduction Plan for Life Insurance Premiums, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 23: Telephone People and the Atomic Bomb, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 24: Agreements Between Michigan Bell Telephone Company and Communications Workers of America, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 25: Plan for Employees' Pensions Disability Benefits and Death Benefits, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 26: Plan for Employees Pensions Disability Benefits and Death Benefits, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 27: Working Agreement Michigan Bell Telephone Co. and Communications Workers of America, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 28: Agreement between Communications Workers of America ans Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Accounting Department, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 29: Agreement between Communications Workers of America and Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Traffic Department, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 30: Agreement between Communications Workers of America and Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Accounting Department, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 31: Agreement between Communications Workers of America and Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Accounting Department, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 32: Agreement between Communications Workers of America and Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Traffic Department, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 33: Working Agreement between Communications Workers of America and Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Plant Department, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 34: Working Agreement between Communications Workers of America and Michigan Bell Telephone Company, CIO, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 35: Agreement between Communications Workers of America and Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Traffic Department, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 36: Agreement between Communications Workers of America and Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Accounting Department, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 37: Facts About Your retirement, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 38: Facts About Your Company's Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 39: Facts About Your Company' Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 40: Catalog of Motion Pictures, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Box 47, Folder (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Agreement Between Parke, Davis & Company and Oil, Chemical & Atomic Workers, International Union, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Agreement Between Parke, Davis & Company and Oil, Chemical & Atomic Workers, International Union, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Agreement Between Parke, Davis & Company and Oil, Chemical & Atomic Workers, International Union, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Agreement Between Parke, Davis & Company and Oil, Chemical & Atomic Workers, International Union, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Agreement Between Parke, Davis & Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Agreement Between Parke, Davis & Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Agreement Between Parke, Davis & Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Agreement Between Parke, Davis & Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Opportunities at Parke Davis & Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Parke Davis & Company Personnel Policies, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Personnel Policies, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Blueprint for Efficiency, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Tuition refund, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Your Pension Plan, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Your Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Your Major Medical Expense Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: This is Parke-Davis, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Your Long Term Disability Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Comprehensive Group Hospital Care m-75 Group, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Future Section, parke Davis Review, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: News and Views, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: News and Views, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: News and Views, Volume 2, Number 1, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: Feature Section, Parke Davis review, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: Feature Section, Parke Davis Review, Volume 30, M=Number 3, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: Parke Davis review, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: Feature Section, Parke Davis Review, Volume 34, Number 4, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: News and Views, Volume 1, Number 4, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 29: News and Views, Volume 2, Number 2, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 30: Lengthening the Life Line, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 31: Parke- Davis Review 29-4, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 32: Management Development Replacement Schedule, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 33: Review and Appraisal of Personnel for Management Development, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 34: Tuition Refund Program, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 35: Building for the Future through management Development, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 36: A Matterof Health, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Box 47, Folder (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: What I saw at Parke, Davis and Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: What I Saw at Parke, Davis & Co., Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: The Story of Parke, Davis & Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: The Story of Parke, Davis & Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Agreement Betwee Parke, Davis & Company and United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Meet Mr. Time Study, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Agreement Between Parke, Davis & Company and Oil, Chemical & Atomic Workers, International Union, C.I.O, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: About Your Insurance, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Your Opinion of Parke-Davis, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Your Opinion of Parke Davis, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: In the Spotlight, You and Parker Davis, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Employees' Penion Plan, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: A Visit to Parke, Davis & Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Absenteeism can be Curtailed, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: How Our Buiness System Operates, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Parke-Davis Employees' Manual, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: The Story of Penicillin S-R, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Review and Appraisal of Personnel for Management development, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: What Industry Expects of Recent College Graduates, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    By Carlton Winsor. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Agreement Between Parke, Davis & Company Workers, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Agreement Effective from July 1, 1941 to July 1, 1942, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Box 47, Folder (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Unity in Management, Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: My Future is with the Management Team United in a Common Effort, Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: My Future is With the Management Team United in a Common Effort, Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Building Rapport with the Academic Community, Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Human relations Training, Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: My Future - is With the Management Team United in a Common Effort, Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Awards Given at NAF Denver Meeting, Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: NAF Bulletin, Volume 1, Number 12, Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: The National Association of Foremen Who's Who, Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: NAF Code of Ethics, Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: NAF Code of Ethics, Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: A Present Day Necessity, Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Manage, Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Manage, Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Box 47, Folder (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship Standards, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Agreement Between Packard Motor Company and International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, Agricultural Implement Workers of America Affiliated with Congress of Industrial Organization, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Information for Packard Employees, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Employee Representation Constitution of the Packard Aid Association, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Agreement Between Packard Motor Car Company and International Union United Automobile, Aircraft Agricultural Implement Workers of America Affiliated with Congress of Industrial Organization and its Local 190, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Report and Findings of a Panel of the National War Labor Board in Certain Disputes Involving Supervisors, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Agreement Between Packard Motor Car Company and International Union United Automobile, Aircraft Agricultural Implement Workers of America Affiliated with Congress of Industrial Organization and its Local 190, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Packard With Length of Service Rules, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Agreement Between Packard Motor Car Company and International Union United Automobile Workers of America Affiliated with Congress of Industrial Organization and its Local 190, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Agreement Between Packard Motor Car Company and International Union United Workers of America Affiliated with Congress of Industrial Organization and its Local 190, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Packard Length-of-Service Rules, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Packard Employees' Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: The Level Production Plan, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Salary Policies, Main Plant, Exempt and Nonexempt Employees, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Salary Policies, Main Plant, Executive, Supervisory and Staff Employees, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Packard Aid Association of Packard Motor car Company Employees, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Union-Management Cooperation in War Production Programs, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Agreement, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
    Between Packard Motor Car Company and International Union United Automobile, Aircraft Agricultural Implement Workers of America Affiliated with Congress of Industrial Organization and its Local 190. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Exhibit D, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Packard Educational Programs, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Agreement Between Packard Motor Car Company and U.A.W-CIO and Its Local No. 190, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Agreement Between Packard Motor Car Company and International Union United Automobile, Aircraft Agricultural Implement Workers of America Affiliated with Congress of Industrial Organization and its Local 190, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: Agreement Between Packard Motor Car Company and International Union United Automobile Workers of America Affiliated with Congress of Industrial Organization and its Local 190, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: Agreement Between Packard Motor Car Company and the International Union United Automobile Workers of America and its Local No. 190, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: Agreement Between Packard Motor Car Company and International Union United Automobile, Aircraft Agricultural Implement Workers of America Affiliated with Congress of Industrial Organization and its Local 190, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: Agreement Between Packard Motor Car Company and International Union United Automobile, Aircraft Agricultural Implement Workers of America Affiliated with Congress of Industrial Organization and its Local 889, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 27: record of Employees, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Box 47, Folder (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Agreement Between Nash-Kelvinator Corporation and International Union, United Automobile, Aircract and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Affiliated with the CIO Local No. 206, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Employees' Association and Factory Council Plan, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Rules, Regulations and Instructions for the Employees of Nash-Kelvinator Corporation, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Agreement Between Nash-Kelvinator Corporation and International Union, United Automobile, Aircract and Agricultural Implement Workers of America Affiliated with the CIO Local No. 206, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: You and Your Job, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: By-Laws of the Ke-Nash-A Club, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Agreement Between Local 72 United Automobile Workers of America CIO and the Nash-Kelvinator corporation Nash Division, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: You and Your Job at Nash kevinator, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Kevinator Corporation Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Pension and Insurance Agreement UAW-CIO and Nash-Kelvinator, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: An Economist's Appraisal of Domestic Elctric refrigeration, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
    By Warren Persons. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Scientific refrigeration in Relation to Nutrition and Health, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
    By Lulu Graves. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Agreement Between the Nash Divisiion of the Nash-kelvinator and the International Union United Automobile Workers of America, and Local No. 72, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Agreement Between Nash-Kelvinator Corporation and the United Automobile Workers of America, Local 206, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Agreement Between Nash-Kelvinator corporation, Kelvinator Division, Grand Rapids Plant, and United Automobile Workers of America, Affiliated with the Congress of Industrial Organization, and its Local No. 206, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Agreement Between the Nash Division of the Nash-Kelvinator Corporation and Lodge No. 34 of the International Association of Machinists, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Box 47, Folder (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Selected Bibliography of African, Asian and Latin American Countries -- Industrial Relations Literature Covering the Period: 1968-1975, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
    By Robert Banks. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Selected Bibliography of Western European Industrial relations Literature Covering the Period 1968-1976, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Glamour for the Girl with a Job, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Human relations in Supervision, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: 1947 Contracts, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Accounting, Traffic and Plant Contracts, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Supervisory Training Material on Company Policies, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Facts About the Benefit Plan for Bell System Men and Women, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Agreement between Communicaions Workers of America, Michigan Division 44 and Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Agreement Between the Communications Workers of America, Michigan Division 44 and the Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Traffic Fepartment, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: You Your Job and Your Company, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Box 48, Folder (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Plan of employee representation, Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: The Yale & Towne Mfg. Co., Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: A History of Standard Oil Company, Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Box 48, Folder (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Employees Representation Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Joint Committee Employees Representation Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Employees Representation Plan for the Plants of Swift & Company, Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: The SOHIO Council Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Social Costs of Instability in Construction: A Preliminary Report, Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Box 48, Folder (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Representation of Employees, Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Plan of Employee Representation, Publication (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Box 48, Folder (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Plan of Employee Representation, Publication (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Box 48, Folder (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Employee Representation Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Box 48, Folder (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Employee Representation on the Pennsylvania Railroad, Publication (Box 48, Folder 6)
    By W.W. Atterbury. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employee Representation on the Pennsylvania Railroad System, Publication (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Experiences of the Pennsylvania Railroad System with Employee Representation, Publication (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: An Employee's View of How the Plan of Employee Representation on the Pennsylvania Railroad Actually Works, Publication (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Box 48, Folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Annual report 1954, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Partnership of Faith, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: How Do You Sell Architects?, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Salaried Position Description, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Non-Contributory Pension Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Salaried Personnel Policie Exempt and Non-Exempt Employees, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Records of Employees, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Studebaker Athletic Association, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Instructions for Performance Review, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Opportunities for College Men, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Studebaker Spotlight, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Insurance Agreement Between the Studebaker corporation and the International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, C.I.O, Local No. 5, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Insurance Agreement Between the Studebaker Corporation and the International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, C.I.O Local No. 5, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Pension Agreement Between the Studebaker Corporation and the International Union, Unied Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: Pension Plan for Houtly-Rated Emplurees of the Studebaker Corporation, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Agreement Between the Studebaker Corporation and UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: Studebaker Communications Primer, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Agreement Between Studebaker Corporation and UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: Apprenticeship Standards, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: Pacific Coast review, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 21: Onan News, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 22: News Releases, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 23: Histoy of Studebaker, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 24: Studebaker Handbook for Salaried employees, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 25: Women for Automotive Maintenance Service, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 26: War Production Work for Studebaker Dealers, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 27: United fund Drive, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 28: Opportunities with te Studebaker Corporation, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 29: Wage Agreement Between the Studebaker Corporation and the International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local no. 1555, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 30: Agreement Between the Studebaker Corpoation and he United Automobile Workers of America Local Union #5, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 31: Industrial relation Policies, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 32: Accident Investigation and Report, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 33: Apprenticeship Training at Studebaker-Packard in South bend, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 34: Agreement of Apprenticeship, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 35: Fringe Benefit Program, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 36: Newest of the New!, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 37: Your Studebaker Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 38: Your Studebaker Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 39: Contributory Retirement Plan for Salaried Employees of Studebaker-Packard Corporation, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 40: Studebaker-UAW Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 41: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Item 42: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 48, Folder 7)